[{"question":"<p><strong>A cliff on the bank of a river is 300m high. If the angle of depression of a point on the opposite side of the river is 60<sup>o<\/sup>, find the width of the river<\/strong><\/p>","options":["150.5m","201.4m","168.7m","173m"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Which of the following expression is not true?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["sin 45 = cos 45","sin (-50) = -sin 50","cos 30 = sin 60","cos (-75) = -cos 75"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>A solid cone has a base radius of 4cm and a vertical height of 9cm. Calculate the volume<\/strong><\/p>","options":["145.5cm<sup>3<\/sup>","173.4cm<sup>3<\/sup>","150.8cm<sup>3<\/sup>","89.1cm<sup>3<\/sup>"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Find the value of x if (x \/ (x+12)) = 7\/14<\/strong><\/p>","options":["9","17","12","15"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>If the radius of a sphere is r = 5.5cm, find its volume<\/strong><\/p>","options":["840.1cm<sup>3<\/sup>","614.5cm<sup>3<\/sup>","924.5cm<sup>3<\/sup>","696.9cm<sup>3<\/sup>"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Given that 1\/4 of 8<sup>y<\/sup> =4<sup>3y<\/sup>. Find y<\/strong><\/p>","options":["-4\/3","-2\/3","3\/2","3\/4"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Given that tan X\u00b0 = 3\/4, calculate the value of sin X\u00b0 + cos X\u00b0<\/strong><\/p>","options":["1.2","1.4","2.5","2.8"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The first term of an A.P. is 5 and the common difference is also 5. What is the mean of the first five terms?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["5","10","15","20"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>If Y = (4-3x)<sup>5<\/sup>, find d<sup>2y<\/sup>\/dx<sup>2<\/sup><\/strong><\/p>","options":["-15(4-3x)<sup>4<\/sup>","20(4-3x)<sup>4<\/sup>","45(4-3x)<sup>4<\/sup>","180(4-3x)<sup>4<\/sup>"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Evaluate&nbsp;&int;cos(2-3x)dx<\/strong><\/p>","options":["-1\/3 Sin(2-3x)","1\/3 Sin(2-3x)","-3 Sin(2-3x)","3 Sin(2-3x)"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>What is the seventh term of the G.P 2, 6, 18,...<\/strong><\/p>","options":["1093","1458","2800","2186"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Find the roots of 3x<sup>2<\/sup> + 5x + 2 = 0<\/strong><\/p>","options":["1 and 3","-1 and -2\/3","1 and 2\/3","2 and -3"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Which of these expressions is not a perfect square?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["x<sup>2<\/sup>-8xy+8","x<sup>2<\/sup>+6xy+9y<sup>2<\/sup>","x<sup>2<\/sup>-10x+25","x<sup>2<\/sup>-8xy+16y<sup>2<\/sup>"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Solve for t in (4\/7t) = 3 \/ (5t-2)<\/strong><\/p>","options":["t=2","t=-8","t=4","t=6"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Okon bought a spare part for his car for N250 but found that it did not fit. He resold it for N200. Find his loss percent<\/strong><\/p>","options":["15%","20%","25%","50%"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Approximate 8.045 to the nearest tens<\/strong><\/p>","options":["8","8.05","10.00","8.045"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>If the probability that John makes addition correctly is 1\/3 and subtraction correctly is 1\/4, what is the probability that he makes 18-16+14 wrongly?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["11\/12","1\/12","3\/5","2\/7"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>What is the number such that when <sup>5<\/sup>\/<sub>6<\/sub> of it is subtracted from 3<sup>1<\/sup>\/<sub>2&nbsp;<\/sub>the result is the same as when <sup>2<\/sup>\/<sub>3<\/sub> of it is added to 2<sup>1<\/sup>\/<sub>2<\/sub><\/strong><\/p>","options":["<sup>5<\/sup>\/<sub>6<\/sub>","<sup>1<\/sup>\/<sub>2<\/sub>","<sup>3<\/sup>\/<sub>6<\/sub>","<sup>2<\/sup>\/<sub>3<\/sub>"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The length of an arc of a circle of radius 3cm is 5<sup>1<\/sup>\/<sub>2<\/sub> cm long. Find the angle which the arc subtends at the center of the circle.<\/strong><\/p>","options":["47.5\u00b0","52.5\u00b0","95\u00b0","105\u00b0"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>If P is a set in a universal set U, simplify (P&cap;\u03d5)<sup>c<\/sup><\/strong><\/p>","options":["\u00b5","\u2205","P","M<sup>c<\/sup>"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Make P the subject of the formula S = (PQ - 2R)(Q - 2R)<\/strong><\/p>","options":["1\/2 R(S + 2RQ + 4R<sup>2<\/sup>)","1\/2 R(S + 2RQ - 4R<sup>2<\/sup>)","1\/2 R(S - 2RQ + 4R<sup>2<\/sup>)","1\/2 R(S - RQ - 4R<sup>2<\/sup>)"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Find the area of rhombus of side 10cm and whose longer diagonal is 16cm long<\/strong><\/p>","options":["80cm<sup>2<\/sup>","96cm<sup>2<\/sup>","100cm<sup>2<\/sup>","160cm<sup>2<\/sup>"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Simplify 0.003025 x 4, leaving your answer in standard form<\/strong><\/p>","options":["1.21 x 10<sup>-4<\/sup>","1.21 x 10<sup>-3<\/sup>","1.21 x x 10<sup>-2<\/sup>","1.21 x 10<sup>-1<\/sup>"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Find the values of t in (3-t) \/ (t<sup>2+2t-15<\/sup>) undefined<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p>&nbsp;<\/p>","options":["-3,5","-5,3","3,5","-3,-5"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Cos 63<sup>o<\/sup> has the same value as<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Cos 27<sup>o<\/sup>","Cos 117<sup>o<\/sup>","Cos 243<sup>o<\/sup>","Cos 297<sup>o<\/sup>"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Calculate the variance of 8,4,6,5 and 2<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p>&nbsp;<\/p>","options":["16","7","4","2"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Evaluate <sup>10<\/sup>P<sub>1<\/sub> x <sup>8<\/sup>C<sub>7<\/sub><\/strong><\/p>","options":["403200","40320","560","80"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Which of the following is a perfect number?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["28","7","4","0"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Find the number of different permutations of letters of the word ABASI<\/strong><\/p>","options":["120","60","30","5"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The cardinality of all the prime members in set A = {1,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10} is<\/strong><\/p>","options":["5","4","10","3"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Simplify log<sub>4<\/sub>8 + log<sub>4<\/sub>10 - log<sub>4<\/sub>5<\/strong><\/p>","options":["log<sub>4<\/sub>13","log16","4","2"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The interior angles of a pentagon are 126\u00b0, 114\u00b0, 83\u00b0, 92\u00b0 and x\u00b0. Find the value of x\u00b0<\/strong><\/p>","options":["125\u00b0","115\u00b0","105\u00b0","85\u00b0"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Express 16.9945 correct to two decimal places.<\/strong><\/p>","options":["17.00","16.99","16.10","17.10"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Find the Geometric Mean of 5 and 20<\/strong><\/p>","options":["12.5","10.0","25.0","15.0"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>If a young boy can ride a bicycle at the rate of 5metres per second, how long will it take him to ride a distance of 12km at the same rate?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["40mins","50mins","30mins","60mins"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Find the mode of the distribution given below;<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>11,49,27,30,11,20,5,11,8,14<\/strong><\/p>","options":["49","11","30","5"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Find x such that sin (3x - 18<sup>o<\/sup>) = sin 39<sup>o<\/sup><\/strong><\/p>","options":["9<sup>o<\/sup>","19<sup>o<\/sup>","12<sup>o<\/sup>","22<sup>o<\/sup>"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Find the gradient of the line joining (-3, -5) and (4, -1)<\/strong><\/p>","options":["4\/7","-4\/7","1 3\/4","-1 3\/4"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>What is the volume of a cone of radius 3(h - 2)cm and height h cm?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["\u03c0h(h - 2)<sup>2<\/sup>cm<sup>3<\/sup>","\u03c0h(h + 2)<sup>2<\/sup>cm<sup>3<\/sup>","3\u03c0h(h - 2)<sup>2<\/sup>cm<sup>3<\/sup>","121\u03c0h(h - 2)<sup>2<\/sup>cm<sup>3<\/sup>"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>A man on a cliff 40m high finds the angle of depression of a boat on the sea to be 30<sup>o<\/sup>. Find the distance of the boat from the foot of the cliff<\/strong><\/p>","options":["(40\u221a3m) \/ 3","40\u221a3m","(50\u221a3m) \/ 3","40m"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The mean of five numbers is x. When the number 12 is added as a 6<sup>th<\/sup> number, the mean of the six numbers is 4.5. What is the value of x?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["2 1\/2","4 1\/2","3","8\/3"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The 1st term of an A.P. is 5 times the common difference, d. Find the 10th term of the sequence in terms of d.<\/strong><\/p>","options":["9d","10d","15d","14d"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Find the sum of the infinite progression; <sup>1<\/sup>\/<sub>2<\/sub> , <sup>1<\/sup>\/<sub>4<\/sub> , <sup>1<\/sup>\/<sub>8<\/sub> , <sup>1<\/sup>\/<sub>16<\/sub> ...<\/strong><\/p>","options":["1","-1","<sup>1<\/sup>\/<sub>2<\/sub>","2"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>What are the prime factors of 2520?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["2,9,10","2,9,17","2,3,5,7,9","2,3,6,9"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Ope deposited N800 in the bank at the rate of 12<sup>1<\/sup>\/<sub>2<\/sub> simple interest. After some time, the total amount was one and half times the principal. <\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>For how many years was the money left in the bank?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["2 2\/3years","12 years","5 1\/2years","8years"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Find the H.C.F of a<sup>2<\/sup>bx + ab<sup>2<\/sup>x and a<sup>2<\/sup>b<sup>3<\/sup>x<\/strong><\/p>","options":["b","a+b","b(a+b)","abx"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Three children shared a basket of oranges in such a way that the first child took 1\/4 of the oranges and the second 3\/4 of the remainder. What fraction of the orange did the third child take?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["3\/16","7\/16","9\/16","13\/16"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Find the sum of the first twenty terms of the arithmetic progression: log a + log a<sup>2<\/sup> + log a<sup>3<\/sup> + . . .<\/strong><\/p>","options":["log a<sup>20<\/sup>","log a<sup>21<\/sup>","log a<sup>200<\/sup>","log a<sup>210<\/sup>"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>A die has four of its faces coloured white and the remaining two coloured black. What is the probability that when the die is thrown two consecutive times, that top face will be white in both cases<\/strong><\/p>","options":["2\/3","1\/9","4\/9","1\/360"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Find the size of each exterior angle of a regular octagon<\/strong><\/p>","options":["45\u00b0","40\u00b0","57\u00b0","36\u00b0"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Simplify (0.06)<sup>2<\/sup> and give your answer correct to 3 significant figures<\/strong><\/p>","options":["0.00036","0.00360","0.004","0.0040"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Solve for P<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong> <sup>2<\/sup>\/<sub>2P - 1<\/sub>  - <sup>5<\/sup>\/<sub>3<\/sub>  = <sup>1<\/sup>\/<sub>P + 2<\/sub><\/strong><\/p>","options":["1, -<sup>5<\/sup>\/<sub>2<\/sub>","-1, <sup>5<\/sup>\/<sub>2<\/sub>","-1, -<sup>5<\/sup>\/<sub>2<\/sub>","1, <sup>5<\/sup>\/<sub>2<\/sub>"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>If M:P = 5:3 and P:R = 4:7, find M:P:R<\/strong><\/p>","options":["35:12:7","20:12:21","15:12:28","8:12:21"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>If g(x-2) = 4x<sup>2<\/sup> + x + 7, find g(1)<\/strong><\/p>","options":["11","21","25","46"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Score&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; 10&nbsp; 9&nbsp; 8&nbsp; 7&nbsp; 6&nbsp; 5&nbsp; 4&nbsp; 3<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>Frequency 1&nbsp; &nbsp;1&nbsp; 3&nbsp; 2&nbsp; 5&nbsp; 7&nbsp; 2&nbsp; 1&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>What is the range of the above distribution?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["35","8","7","5"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Assuming that a leap year contains exactly 366 days. What is the probability that a person will NOT die on his birthday?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["1","365\/366","1\/366","0"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Which of the following is NOT a measure of dispersion?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Variance","Sum of deviations from the mean","Quartile range","Lower quartile"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>In a pie chart, the value of a variable is represented by<\/strong><\/p>","options":["the area of the circle","the circumference of a circle","the area of a sector","the angle of a sector"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>P and Q are mutually exclusive events. The probability of each of them occuring is 1\/3. What is the probability that neither of them occurs?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["0","1\/9","2\/3","4\/9"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>r, s and t are three vectors given by 4i+j, 3i+2j and -4i+j respectively. Find r+s+t<\/strong><\/p>","options":["2i + 4j","3i + 4j","5i - 3j","4i - 3j"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>If the root of the equation 2x<sup>2<\/sup> - 3x + r = 0 are equal, find the value of the constant r<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p>&nbsp;<\/p>","options":["9\/8","8\/9","3\/4","4\/3"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Solve the simultaneous equations x<sup>2<\/sup> - y<sup>2<\/sup> = 15 and x+y = 5. Find the value of x-y<\/strong><\/p>","options":["20","10","5","3"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>In a class of 33 students, 18 play football, 12 play basket ball and 7 play both games. How many students play none of the two games?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["3","8","10","5"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>If log<sub>x<\/sub>16 - log<sub>x<\/sub>8 = 1, find x<\/strong><\/p>","options":["4","2","10","5"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>A chord AB of length 8cm is placed in a circle of radius 8cm. Calculate the angle the chord subtends at the center of the circle.<\/strong><\/p>","options":["64\u00b0","56\u00b0","60\u00b0","72\u00b0"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Three people share 40 oranges in the ratio 1:3:4. How many oranges did the second get?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["12","18","10","15"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Solve the equations for x and y<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>2<sup>x+y<\/sup> = 16 ... (i)<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>3<sup>2x+y&nbsp;<\/sup>= 9 ...&nbsp; &nbsp;(ii)<\/strong><\/p>","options":["x=2, y=3","x=4, y=-1","x=-3, y=4","x=-2, y=6"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>If it takes 8 people 20 days to complete a job, how long will 5 people take to complete the same job?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["32 days","25 days","28 days","36 days"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Find the 8th term of the following geometric progression 1, 2, 4, 8, 16...<\/strong><\/p>","options":["120","144","132","128"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>A bicycle shop owner has 12 mountain bicycles in the showroom. The owner wishes to select 5 of them to display at a bicycle show. How many different ways can a group of 5 bicycles be selected?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["800","792","720","680"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Find the zeros of the function y= x<sup>2<\/sup> - 3x + 2<\/strong><\/p>","options":["0,1","1,2","-1,3","2,-3"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>A piece of cloth was measured as 6.10m, if the actual length of the cloth is 6.35m, find the percentage error, correct to 2 decimal places<\/strong><\/p>","options":["3.05%","3.94%","15.00%","25%"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Solve the equation 5x<sup>2<\/sup> - 4x - 1 = 0<\/strong><\/p>","options":["1, 1\/5","-1, -1\/5","1, 1\/5","-1\/5"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Make R the subject of formula I = (PxRxT) \/ 100<\/strong><\/p>","options":["R = (100I) \/ PT","R = (100T) \/ RI","R = (100P) \/ I","R = (PRT) \/ 100"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The radius of circle is 3.5cm. Find the area of the circle<\/strong><\/p>","options":["38.5cm<sup>2<\/sup>","3.85cm<sup>2<\/sup>","385cm<sup>2<\/sup>","0.385cm<sup>2<\/sup>"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>If 612 nuts are divided among three men P, Q and R in the ratio 8:5:4, how many nuts does R receive?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["144","180","216","288"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Express as a single fraction (x\/(x-2)) - ((x+2)\/(x+3))<\/strong><\/p>","options":["(2x<sup>2<\/sup>-3x-4) \/ (x-2)(x+3)","(2x<sup>2<\/sup>+3x-4) \/ (x-2)(x+3)","2 \/ (x-2)(x+3)","none"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Marks&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; 0&nbsp; 1&nbsp; &nbsp;2&nbsp; &nbsp; 3&nbsp; &nbsp; 4&nbsp; &nbsp;5<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>Frequency 4&nbsp; 7&nbsp; 12&nbsp; 18&nbsp; 11&nbsp; 8<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>The mode of the above distribution is<\/strong><\/p>","options":["3","5","8","18"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Marks&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; 0&nbsp; 1&nbsp; &nbsp;2&nbsp; &nbsp; 3&nbsp; &nbsp; 4&nbsp; &nbsp;5<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>Frequency 4&nbsp; 7&nbsp; 12&nbsp; 18&nbsp; 11&nbsp; 8<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>The mean of the above distribution is<\/strong><\/p>","options":["2.82","5.82","8.2","1.82"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Three men Bedu, Bakare and Kofi share N500 in the ratio 3:2:x respectively. If Bedu's share is N50, find the value of x<\/strong><\/p>","options":["10","40","25","60"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Simplify (1<sup>2<\/sup>\/<sub>3<\/sub>) - <sup>2<\/sup>\/<sub>3<\/sub><\/strong><\/p>","options":["2 <sup>1<\/sup>\/<sub>3<\/sub>","<sup>1<\/sup>\/<sub>3<\/sub>","1","<sup>3<\/sup>\/<sub>7<\/sub>"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The square root of a number is 2k. What is half of the number?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["\u221ak\/2","\u221ak","1\/2k<sup>2<\/sup>","2k<sup>2<\/sup>"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>A cooperative society charges an interest of 5<sup>1<\/sup>\/<sub>2<\/sub>% per annum on any amount borrowed by its members. If a member borrows N125,000.00, how much does he pay back after one year?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["136,875","131,875","128,750","126,250"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>T varies directly as D and inversely as A. Given that T=6, D=3 and A=2, find A when T=3 and D=6<\/strong><\/p>","options":["6","8","2","24"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Calculate, without using table Tan 45<sup>o<\/sup> + Cos 60<sup>0<\/sup><\/strong><\/p>","options":["\u221a3-1 \/ 2","1\/2","1<sup>1<\/sup>\/<sub>2<\/sub>","\u221a3\/2"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Solve the equation 10 + 3x - x<sup>2<\/sup> = 0<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p>&nbsp;<\/p>","options":["x=2 or -5","x= -2 or 5","x = -1 or 10","x = 2 of 5"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Factorize 27P<sup>2<\/sup>x<sup>2<\/sup> - 48y<sup>2<\/sup><\/strong><\/p>","options":["9(3Px-4y)","3(3Px-4y)(3Px-4y)","9(Px-4y)(3Px+4y)","3(3Px-4y)(3Px+4y)"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Find the average of the first four prime numbers greater than 10<\/strong><\/p>","options":["20","19","17","15"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"}]